Guide to the Cornell University College of Veterinary Medicine Alumni Files, 1876-
Cornell University College of Veterinary Medicine Alumni Files, 1876-
- Series II. 1900-1999
  - 1940-1949
    - Baker, James Andrew, 1940 (Box 8, Folder 52)
      1910-1975
    - Bergerson, John Russell, 1940 (Box 8, Folder 53)
    - Boynton, James Webster, 1940 (Box 8, Folder 54)
      1918-1988
    - Combs, Margaret Esther O'Brien, 1940 (Box 8, Folder 55)
      1917-
      Twelfth woman graduate
    - Doremus, Helen M. Borchmann, 1940 (Box 8, Folder 56)
      1918-2002
      Thirteenth woman graduate
    - Fake, Lynn Bacon, 1940 (Box 8, Folder 57)
      1917-1950
    - Favata, Anthony Frederic, 1940 (Box 8, Folder 58)
      1918-2003
    - Ganis [Gangarosa], Ralph Louis, 1940 (Box 8, Folder 59)
      1918-1957
    - Groten [Grotenstein], Harris Harold, 1940 (Box 8, Folder 60)
    - Guile, Harlan Switzer, 1940 (Box 8, Folder 61)
      1913-1961
    - Jordan, Clarence Arthur, 1940 (Box 8, Folder 62)
    - Kahl, Paul L., 1940 (Box 8, Folder 63)
      1916-1998
    - Kelsey, Carleton Richard, 1940 (Box 8, Folder 64)
      1916-2009
    - Kopp, Moe, 1940 (Box 8, Folder 65)
    - Laughlin, Cyril John, 1940 (Box 8, Folder 66)
    - Leonard, Elwin Nancarrow, 1940 (Box 8, Folder 67)
    - Lloyd, Rebecca Gifford, 1940 (Box 8, Folder 68)
      Fourteenth woman graduate
    - Lombard, Ferdinand Anthony, 1940 (Box 8, Folder 69)
    - Loomis, Ralph Eugene, 1940 (Box 8, Folder 70)
    - Mayer, Karl, 1940 (Box 8, Folder 71)
    - McBride, Garry V., Jr., 1940 (Box 8, Folder 72)
    - McClelland, Frank Edwin, Jr., 1940 (Box 8, Folder 73)
    - Oppenheimer, Russell Braun, 1940 (Box 8, Folder 74)
    - Paciello, Vincent Xavier, 1940 (Box 8, Folder 75)
      1915-2009
    - Payton [Patashnick], Jerome, 1940 (Box 8, Folder 76)
    - Polansky, Emily Gordon Chickering, 1940 (Box 8, Folder 77)
      Fifteenth woman graduate
    - Potter, Carleton Wilburn, 1940 (Box 8, Folder 78)
    - Richtscheid, Adam George, 1940 (Box 8, Folder 79)
      1916-1940
    - Rosen, Bernard William, 1940 (Box 8, Folder 80)
    - Sawyer, John Edwin, 1940 (Box 8, Folder 81)
      1914-1961
    - Shear, Herbert, 1940 (Box 8, Folder 82)
    - Skinner, Norman Ely, 1940 (Box 8, Folder 83)
    - Sullivan, George Joseph, 1940 (Box 8, Folder 84)
    - Thompsett, Robert Evan, 1940 (Box 8, Folder 85)
    - Vogel, Allan A., 1940 (Box 8, Folder 86)
    - White, Lee Roswell, 1940 (Box 8, Folder 87)
      1915-1963
    - Wingerter, Emery George, 1940 (Box 8, Folder 88)
    - Wiswall, Roscoe George, 1940 (Box 8, Folder 89)
      1919-2002
      See also 1940 Ashman, Robert Irving
    - Witter, Ralph Edward, 1940 (Box 8, Folder 90)
      1916-1971
    - Ackerman, Anthony Joseph, 1941 (Box 8, Folder 91)
      1919-
    - Bender [Bendursky], Samuel, 1941 (Box 8, Folder 92)
    - Britton, John Wanger, 1941 (Box 8, Folder 93)
    - Bryan, Donald Irving, 1941 (Box 8, Folder 94)
    - Charles, Arthur Sheldon, 1941 (Box 8, Folder 95)
    - Connor, Alexander, 1941 (Box 8, Folder 96)
      1920-
    - Dean, Donald Joseph, 1941 (Box 8, Folder 97)
    - Earl, Alfred Ellsworth, 1941 (Box 8, Folder 98)
    - Everly, William Parkinson, 1941 (Box 8, Folder 99)
    - Fales, Roger Richard, 1941 (Box 8, Folder 100)
      1917-2010
    - Ferris, Joseph, 1941 (Box 8, Folder 101)
    - Fobian, Vernon Christian, 1941 (Box 8, Folder 102)
      1917-1973
    - Harmon, Karl Storer, 1941 (Box 8, Folder 103)
      1907-1988
    - Helsel, Harry Joseph, 1941 (Box 8, Folder 104)
    - Howard [Horowitz], Nathan Zachary, 1941 (Box 8, Folder 105)
    - Linden, Benjamin, 1941 (Box 8, Folder 106)
    - Maxwell, Henry, 1941 (Box 8, Folder 107)
    - McKinney, George Voorheis, 1941 (Box 8, Folder 108)
    - Meisels, Morton, 1941 (Box 8, Folder 109)
      1915-2001
    - Mick, Louis William, 1941 (Box 8, Folder 110)
      1917-2002
    - Milks, Richard Vose, 1941 (Box 8, Folder 111)
    - Papish, Philip George, 1941 (Box 8, Folder 112)
    - Peppe, Vincent John, 1941 (Box 8, Folder 113)
      1918-1997
    - Polansky, Henry, 1941 (Box 8, Folder 114)
    - Rice, Alvin Whitney, 1941 (Box 8, Folder 115)
    - Risley, Henry Brainard, 1941 (Box 8, Folder 116)
    - Sheridan, Gerald Haynes, 1941 (Box 8, Folder 117)
    - Simmons, Eric Whiting, 1941 (Box 8, Folder 118)
    - Siver, Dougal Harvey, 1941 (Box 8, Folder 119)
    - Snyder, Leon Donald, 1941 (Box 8, Folder 120)
    - Spanier, Seymour Edward, 1941 (Box 8, Folder 121)
    - Steinfeldt, Edward Frederick, 1941 (Box 8, Folder 122)
      1919-2006
    - Sylstra, Anthony, 1941 (Box 8, Folder 123)
    - Tucker, Edgar "Brud" Wesley, 1941 (Box 9, Folder 1)
      1917-1994
    - Udall, Robert Hovey, 1941 (Box 9, Folder 2)
      1916-2001
      Various photographs & CD-ROM disc
    - Williamson, James R. [Guglielmino, Angelo Jose], 1941 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Woodruff, Raymond Arthur, 1941 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Wright, Frederick O., 1941 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Armstrong, James, 1942 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Baxter, Clinton M., 1942 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - Blostein, Leon E., 1942 (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Buist, Jean Mackerley, 1942 (Box 9, Folder 9)
      1919-2008
      No class photo; Sixteenth woman graduate
    - Comin, Ralph, 1942 (Box 9, Folder 10)
      1917-1961
    - Fraser, Gordon Stewart, 1942 (Box 9, Folder 11)
      1912-1960
    - Gilmour, Judd T., 1942 (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - Haller, Christian Joseph, 1942 (Box 9, Folder 13)
      1918-2009
    - Handler, Paul, 1942 (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - Jones, Arthur J., 1942 (Box 9, Folder 15)
    - Kane, Joseph Robert, 1942 (Box 9, Folder 16)
    - Kopp, Harold, 1942 (Box 9, Folder 17)
    - Lasher, Hiram Nelson, 1942 (Box 9, Folder 18)
    - Leahy, Charles R., 1942 (Box 9, Folder 19)
      1914-2000
    - Leveson, Lawrence, 1942 (Box 9, Folder 20)
    - Loomis, Grace Kinney, 1942 (Box 9, Folder 21)
      Seventeenth woman graduate
    - Martin, Ansel Robert, 1942 (Box 9, Folder 22)
    - Maschgan, Erich Richard, 1942 (Box 9, Folder 23)
    - May, Robert Eugene, 1942 (Box 9, Folder 24)
    - Mick, Lester H., 1942 (Box 9, Folder 25)
    - Morse, Guy E., 1942 (Box 9, Folder 26)
      1917-2000
    - Muskus, Claudio E., 1942 (Box 9, Folder 27)
      1918-1964
    - Newton, Wright I., 1942 (Box 9, Folder 28)
      1917-1984
    - Peterson, Elwin Herbert, 1942 (Box 9, Folder 29)
      1909-1994
    - Phelps, Harold C., 1942 (Box 9, Folder 30)
      1919-1996
    - Proctor, Delano Lightner, Jr., 1942 (Box 9, Folder 31)
      Various photographs; AVMA president 1985-1986
    - Pulling, Fred Bunnell, Jr., 1942 (Box 9, Folder 32)
      1918-2007
    - Rieber, Jesse Paul, 1942 (Box 9, Folder 33)
    - Rubenstein [Robins], Abraham M., 1942 (Box 9, Folder 34)
    - Sann, Benjamin, 1942 (Box 9, Folder 35)
      1916-2008
    - Saunders, Richard, 1942 (Box 9, Folder 36)
    - Scheffler, Harold George, 1942 (Box 9, Folder 37)
      1919-2005
    - Schwobel, Wilbur Peter, 1942 (Box 9, Folder 38)
      1916-2006
    - Smith, Merwin Gsell, 1942 (Box 9, Folder 39)
    - Smith, Robert D., 1942 (Box 9, Folder 40)
      1912-1968
    - Somers, Gerald [Solmitz, Gerhard S.], 1942 (Box 9, Folder 41)
    - Steed, Donald J., 1942 (Box 9, Folder 42)
    - Ucko, Peter W., 1942 (Box 9, Folder 43)
    - Vedder, Charles D., 1942 (Box 9, Folder 44)
    - Wager, Leslie Allen, 1942 (Box 9, Folder 45)
    - Weiss, Leonard, 1942 (Box 9, Folder 46)
    - White, Howard Stinson, 1942 (Box 9, Folder 47)
      1907-1981
    - Wuori, Leo Adolf, 1942 (Box 9, Folder 48)
      1919-2003
    - Adolph, William Henry, Jr., 1943 (Feb) (Box 9, Folder 49)
    - Arnaboldi, Allan Charles, 1943 (Feb) (Box 9, Folder 50)
    - Becker, Milford Earl, 1943 (Feb) (Box 9, Folder 51)
    - Brungot, Norman Stanley, 1943 (Feb) (Box 9, Folder 52)
    - Burghardt, Harry Frederick, 1943 (Feb) (Box 9, Folder 53)
      1920-2003
    - Cleveland, Howard Joseph, 1943 (Feb) (Box 9, Folder 54)
      1919-1989
    - Conklin, Erwin Arthur, 1943 (Feb) (Box 9, Folder 55)
    - Dillmann, Eugene George, 1943 (Feb) (Box 9, Folder 56)
    - Fisher, Bernard, 1943 (Feb) (Box 9, Folder 57)
    - Gilbert, Edwin Ormont, 1943 (Feb) (Box 9, Folder 58)
    - Gumaer, Kenneth Irving, 1943 (Feb) (Box 9, Folder 59)
    - Halpin, George Doyle, 1943 (Feb) (Box 9, Folder 60)
    - Haner, Frank Henry, Jr., 1943 (Feb) (Box 9, Folder 61)
      1917-2006
    - Hokanson, John Francis, 1943 (Feb) (Box 9, Folder 62)
    - Hopper, Henry Dean, 1943 (Feb) (Box 9, Folder 63)
    - Huckle, John James, 1943 (Feb) (Box 9, Folder 64)
      1922-
    - Jenkins, DuBois LeFevre, 1943 (Feb) (Box 9, Folder 65)
      1920-2010
    - Kiesel, George Kuhn, 1943 (Feb) (Box 9, Folder 66)
      1917-1986
    - Kotchek, Leo, 1943 (Feb) (Box 9, Folder 67)
    - Lanfair, Clyde Everett, 1943 (Feb) (Box 9, Folder 68)
      1921-2013
    - Larson, Leonard John, 1943 (Feb) (Box 9, Folder 69)
    - Lewis, Norman Francis, 1943 (Feb) (Box 9, Folder 70)
    - Lindsey, Lionel Woodrow, 1943 (Feb) (Box 9, Folder 71)
      1917-2007
    - Lipman, Bernard, 1943 (Feb) (Box 9, Folder 72)
    - Majilton, Edward Anderson, 1943 (Feb) (Box 9, Folder 73)
      1919-1997
    - Matuszak, Walter John, 1943 (Feb) (Box 9, Folder 74)
      1918-2001
    - McKown, Donald Claude, 1943 (Feb) (Box 9, Folder 75)
      1918-1995
    - Paddock, Nicholas McKie, 1943 (Feb) (Box 9, Folder 76)
      1920-1968
    - Phillips, Webster Vernon, 1943 (Feb) (Box 9, Folder 77)
      1919-1992
    - Proper, John Shepard, 1943 (Feb) (Box 9, Folder 78)
      1920-2001
    - Ross, Andre Moul, 1943 (Feb) (Box 9, Folder 79)
      Eighteenth woman graduate
    - Ruebush, Ephraim Edgar, Jr., 1943 (Feb) (Box 9, Folder 80)
    - Tymchyn, Victor John, 1943 (Feb) (Box 9, Folder 81)
    - Ulrich, Carlton Louis, 1943 (Feb) (Box 9, Folder 82)
    - Woolfe, Daniel T., 1943 (Feb) (Box 9, Folder 83)
    - Young, George A., Jr., 1943 (Feb) (Box 9, Folder 84)
      1917-1964
    - Zimmerman, Theodore, 1943 (Feb) (Box 9, Folder 85)
      1919-2013
    - Arnaboldi, Joseph Paul, 1943 (Oct) (Box 9, Folder 86)
    - Bandes, Gerald Harry, 1943 (Oct) (Box 9, Folder 87)
      1921-
    - Berdan, Leonard Nellis, 1943 (Oct) (Box 9, Folder 88)
    - Boardman, Don Arol, Jr., 1943 (Oct) (Box 9, Folder 89)
    - Coye, Elmer Nathan, 1943 (Oct) (Box 9, Folder 90)
      1921-2003
    - Crawford, Everett John, 1943 (Oct) (Box 9, Folder 91)
      1921-2009
    - Doig, Robert Speer, 1943 (Oct) (Box 9, Folder 92)
      1919-2010
    - Dragoo, Paul Orloff, 1943 (Oct) (Box 9, Folder 93)
    - Elmer, Everett Kermit, 1943 (Oct) (Box 9, Folder 94)
      1920-2008
    - Ferber, Leonard, 1943 (Oct) (Box 9, Folder 95)
    - Fish, Richard Barrett, 1943 (Oct) (Box 9, Folder 96)
      1921-2002
    - Gage, Thomas Asa, 1943 (Oct) (Box 9, Folder 97)
      1918-1968
    - Gillespie, Richard Joseph, 1943 (Oct) (Box 9, Folder 98)
    - Goldberg, Abie, 1943 (Oct) (Box 9, Folder 99)
    - Goodman, Merrill, 1943 (Oct) (Box 9, Folder 100)
      1918-1958
    - Goss, Allen Carlyle, 1943 (Oct) (Box 9, Folder 101)
      1922-2010
    - Grover, Boynton Arnold, 1943 (Oct) (Box 9, Folder 102)
      1920-2012
    - Jastremski, Maurice Michael, 1943 (Oct) (Box 9, Folder 103)
      1916-1987
    - Jones, Wallace Gordon, 1943 (Oct) (Box 9, Folder 104)
    - Karmin, Leo Raymond, 1943 (Oct) (Box 9, Folder 105)
    - Malmberg, Rex Albert, 1943 (Oct) (Box 9, Folder 106)
    - Palmer, Hallsey Ralph, 1943 (Oct) (Box 9, Folder 107)
      1921-2012
    - Parmelee, Richard Hall, Jr., 1943 (Oct) (Box 9, Folder 108)
    - Radzwiller, Saul [Racliffe, Paul A.], 1943 (Oct) (Box 9, Folder 109)
    - Richards, John William, Jr., 1943 (Oct) (Box 9, Folder 110)
      1918-1971
    - Rickard, Charles Glenwood, 1943 (Oct) (Box 9, Folder 111)
      1922-1993
      See also Faculty file and Collection #24-7-3546, Rickard, Charles G., papers, 1941-1942
    - Ripps, Jerome Harold, 1943 (Oct) (Box 9, Folder 112)
      1919-1980
    - Robertson, Colin Mitchell, 1943 (Oct) (Box 10, Folder 1)
      1921-2011
    - Simpson, Charles Floyd, 1943 (Oct) (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Smallridge, Dorothy E. Bradley, 1943 (Oct) (Box 10, Folder 3)
      Nineteenth woman graduate
    - Smith, Edwin Browning, 1943 (Oct) (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Studdert, Hugh Patrick, 1943 (Oct) (Box 10, Folder 5)
      1920-1991
    - Tanis, John, 1943 (Oct) (Box 10, Folder 6)
      1921-1985
    - Troy, Matthew Alan, 1943 (Oct) (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Tweddle, John Richard, 1943 (Oct) (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Vail, John Irving, 1943 (Oct) (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - Zepp, Clarence Peter, Jr., 1943 (Oct) (Box 10, Folder 10)
      1922-1979
    - Baker, DeWitt T., 1944 (Box 10, Folder 11)
      1921-2010
    - Basom, Richard Russell, 1944 (Box 10, Folder 12)
      1923-
    - Bentinck-Smith, John, 1944 (Box 10, Folder 13)
      See also faculty file
    - Berman, David Theodore, 1944 (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - Byrne, Robert Joseph, 1944 (Box 10, Folder 15)
    - Clement, Edwin Prescott, 1944 (Box 10, Folder 16)
    - Davis, Arthur Edwin, 1944 (Box 10, Folder 17)
    - Delahanty, Donald Dee, 1944 (Box 10, Folder 18)
      1923-1975
    - Erb, Frederick Austin, 1944 (Box 10, Folder 19)
    - Flint, Jack Gregory, 1944 (Box 10, Folder 20)
      1919-2012
    - Haller, Clyde Manford, 1944 (Box 10, Folder 21)
      1923-2013
    - Hartley, Clinton Eugene, 1944 (Box 10, Folder 22)
    - Hoag, Warren George, 1944 (Box 10, Folder 23)
    - Holden, Chester James, 1944 (Box 10, Folder 24)
    - King, Anne Hastings Gott, 1944 (Box 10, Folder 25)
      Twenthieth woman graduate
    - King, William Patrick, 1944 (Box 10, Folder 26)
    - Lawrence [Lipsky], David E., 1944 (Box 10, Folder 27)
    - Leonard, Harmon Cook, 1944 (Box 10, Folder 28)
      1920-2014
    - Lipman, Arthur, 1944 (Box 10, Folder 29)
    - Lockwood, Floyd Addison, 1944 (Box 10, Folder 30)
      1919-2009
    - Logue, Jeanne Martha Neubecker, 1944 (Box 10, Folder 31)
      Twenty first woman graduate
    - Lukens, Walter Benedict, 1944 (Box 10, Folder 32)
    - Maker, Wilber Cushing, 1944 (Box 10, Folder 33)
      1922-2006
    - McEntee, Kenneth B., 1944 (Box 10, Folder 34)
      1921-2005
    - McEvoy, Richard Kane, 1944 (Box 10, Folder 35)
    - Mettler, John Joseph, Jr., 1944 (Box 10, Folder 36)
      1923-2001
    - Moore, Lloyd Edward, Jr., 1944 (Box 10, Folder 37)
      1923-1998
    - Morse, Erskine Vance, 1944 (Box 10, Folder 38)
      1921-1995
    - O'Dea, Joseph Charles, 1944 (Box 10, Folder 39)
      1921-2006
      U.S. Olympic Games veterinarian
    - Patton, Herbert William, 1944 (Box 10, Folder 40)
    - Porter, David B., 1944 (Box 10, Folder 41)
      1922-1992
    - Povar, Morris Leon, 1944 (Box 10, Folder 42)
      1920-2013
    - Randolph [Williamson], Florence E. Keith, 1944 (Box 10, Folder 43)
      Twenty second woman graduate
    - Rappaport, George Elliott, 1944 (Box 10, Folder 44)
    - Reed, George E., 1944 (Box 10, Folder 45)
    - Robinson, Charles Richard, 1944 (Box 10, Folder 46)
      1923-2010
    - Rossoff, Irving Sylvius, 1944 (Box 10, Folder 47)
      1921-2007
    - Santivanez, Jose, 1944 (Box 10, Folder 48)
      From Peru
    - Sayres, Joseph Patrick, 1944 (Box 10, Folder 49)
    - Tillou, Donald Albert, 1944 (Box 10, Folder 50)
      1922-1996
    - Van Deusen, Carlisle Watson, 1944 (Box 10, Folder 51)
    - Vaughn, Thurman Church, Jr., 1944 (Box 10, Folder 52)
    - Whitehead, Roland Grant, 1944 (Box 10, Folder 53)
    - Young, Clayton Samuel, 1944 (Box 10, Folder 54)
      1922-1977
    - Bartz, Norman William, 1945 (Feb) (Box 10, Folder 55)
    - Berrigan, Martin Vincent, 1945 (Feb) (Box 10, Folder 56)
    - Beyer, Theodore John, 1945 (Feb) (Box 10, Folder 57)
      1923-2011
    - Colvin, Ashel Stanton, 1945 (Feb) (Box 10, Folder 58)
      1923-2007
    - Drew, Donald Roe, 1945 (Feb) (Box 10, Folder 59)
    - Duncan, Charles Stuart, 1945 (Feb) (Box 10, Folder 60)
    - Evans, Alvin Stanley, 1945 (Feb) (Box 10, Folder 61)
    - Greer, Russell Flagg, 1945 (Feb) (Box 10, Folder 62)
    - Haifleigh, William James, 1945 (Feb) (Box 10, Folder 63)
    - Harmon, Howard, 1945 (Feb) (Box 10, Folder 64)
    - Jones, Russell Kay, 1945 (Feb) (Box 10, Folder 65)
      1922-1998
    - Kiehle, Kenneth Lee, 1945 (Feb) (Box 10, Folder 66)
      1923-2004
    - Kraft, Lisbeth Martha, 1945 (Feb) (Box 10, Folder 67)
      1920-2002
      Twenty third woman graduate
    - Langman, James Hanford, 1945 (Feb) (Box 10, Folder 68)
    - Lewis, Gilbert, 1945 (Feb) (Box 10, Folder 69)
    - Lewis, Ralph Wesley, 1945 (Feb) (Box 10, Folder 70)
      1922-1995
    - Liebig, Philip Henry, 1945 (Feb) (Box 10, Folder 71)
    - Lopez, Robert Albert, 1945 (Feb) (Box 10, Folder 72)
      1922-2007
    - Lynch, Thomas Joseph, 1945 (Feb) (Box 10, Folder 73)
    - McMurray, Homer Francis, 1945 (Feb) (Box 10, Folder 74)
    - Mitchell, Grayson Bates, 1945 (Feb) (Box 10, Folder 75)
      1922-2005
    - Morrow, Gordon Gifford, 1945 (Feb) (Box 10, Folder 76)
      1922-1997
    - Radcliffe, Harry, 1945 (Feb) (Box 10, Folder 77)
    - Ritter, Andrew Samuel, 1945 (Feb) (Box 10, Folder 78)
    - Shaffer, Joseph Cecil, 1945 (Feb) (Box 10, Folder 79)
    - Stein, Hermann Bernard, 1945 (Feb) (Box 10, Folder 80)
    - Walker, Robert David, 1945 (Feb) (Box 10, Folder 81)
    - Watson, James Paul, 1945 (Feb) (Box 10, Folder 82)
    - Wester, Ralph Foster, 1945 (Feb) (Box 10, Folder 83)
    - Wilcox, Harrison Jesse, Jr., 1945 (Feb) (Box 10, Folder 84)
    - Zellner, Carleton Martin, 1945 (Feb) (Box 10, Folder 85)
      1923-2003
    - Abbott, George Wells, 1945 (Oct) (Box 10, Folder 86)
      1922-2009
    - Bartle, Francis Guy, 1945 (Oct) (Box 10, Folder 87)
      1924-
    - Bower, Stanton Ellsworth, 1945 (Oct) (Box 10, Folder 88)
    - Bush, Neill Earl, 1945 (Oct) (Box 10, Folder 89)
      1920-1992
    - Cummings, Harold James, 1945 (Oct) (Box 10, Folder 90)
      1920-2009
    - Dimon, Myron Loyal, 1945 (Oct) (Box 10, Folder 91)
    - Dubin, Theodore, 1945 (Oct) (Box 10, Folder 92)
    - Fox, Francis Henry, 1945 (Oct) (Box 10, Folder 93)
      1923-2015
    - Goebel, John David, 1945 (Oct) (Box 10, Folder 94)
    - Goode, George Alfred, 1945 (Oct) (Box 10, Folder 95)
    - Hartenstein, Chester, 1945 (Oct) (Box 10, Folder 96)
    - Herlitz, George Hans, 1945 (Oct) (Box 10, Folder 97)
    - Horton, Robert Ellsworth, 1945 (Oct) (Box 10, Folder 98)
    - Kandl, John Frederick, 1945 (Oct) (Box 10, Folder 99)
    - Klein, Walter Marvin, 1945 (Oct) (Box 10, Folder 100)
    - MacCallum, Alexander Duncan, 1945 (Oct) (Box 10, Folder 101)
    - Marshak, Robert Reuben, 1945 (Oct) (Box 10, Folder 102)
    - McBee, John Adair, 1945 (Oct) (Box 10, Folder 103)
    - Mellon, Ward Eichler, 1945 (Oct) (Box 10, Folder 104)
    - Palmiter, Richard Leslie, 1945 (Oct) (Box 10, Folder 105)
    - Ross, Michael, 1945 (Oct) (Box 10, Folder 106)
    - Seader, Saul Bernard, 1945 (Oct) (Box 10, Folder 107)
    - Shigley, Robert Fremont, 1945 (Oct) (Box 10, Folder 108)
    - Smith, Harry Norman, 1945 (Oct) (Box 10, Folder 109)
      1922-2012
    - Smithcors, James Frederick, 1945 (Oct) (Box 10, Folder 110)
      1920-2006
    - VanGelder, Richard Frank, 1945 (Oct) (Box 10, Folder 111)
      1924-2000
    - Vetter, Roland Frederick, 1945 (Oct) (Box 10, Folder 112)
    - Wallace, Carl Nelson, 1945 (Oct) (Box 10, Folder 113)
    - Watts, Minor Frederick, 1945 (Oct) (Box 10, Folder 114)
    - Wheat, John Donald, 1945 (Oct) (Box 10, Folder 115)
      1923-2009
    - Bardwell, Robert Edward, 1946 (Box 10, Folder 116)
    - Batchelder, Roger Williams, 1946 (Box 10, Folder 117)
      1925-
    - Brightenback, George Edward, 1946 (Box 10, Folder 118)
      1922-1991
    - Brown, Philip Raymond, 1946 (Box 10, Folder 119)
      1924-1974?
    - Cohen, Hunter, 1946 (Box 10, Folder 120)
    - Delano, Ray Osborne, Jr., 1946 (Box 10, Folder 121)
    - Denk, Adolph John, 1946 (Box 10, Folder 122)
    - Doremus, Henry Meade, 1946 (Box 10, Folder 123)
    - Dorn, Saul James, 1946 (Box 10, Folder 124)
    - Field, Robert Althans, 1946 (Box 10, Folder 125)
    - Forsyth, Rodney Anson, 1946 (Box 10, Folder 126)
      1922-1970
    - Fountain, Edmund Louis, 1946 (Box 10, Folder 127)
    - Haberman, Julius Jay, 1946 (Box 10, Folder 128)
      1921-2008
    - Hoffmire, James Henry, 1946 (Box 10, Folder 129)
    - Icken, Donald Frederick, 1946 (Box 10, Folder 130)
      1924-1998
    - Irving, Elwyn Laverne, 1946 (Box 10, Folder 131)
    - Jenkins, Charles Murray, 1946 (Box 10, Folder 132)
    - Kaplan, William, 1946 (Box 10, Folder 133)
      1922-2008
      See also Collection #37-5-3975, Kaplan, William, papers, 1960s-1980s
    - Kirk, Robert Warren, 1946 (Box 10, Folder 134)
      1922-2011
      See also Faculty file and Collection #24-02-3372, Kirk, Robert W. papers, 1946-2004
    - Love, Thomas Jack, 1946 (Box 10, Folder 135)
      1921-2004
    - Lynch, Donald Richard, 1946 (Box 10, Folder 136)
      1921-2000
    - MacCallum, Janet Ann Meade, 1946 (Box 10, Folder 137)
      Twenty fourth woman graduate
    - McAvoy, Byron Gotham, 1946 (Box 11, Folder 1)
      1924-2014
    - McCann, John William, 1946 (Box 11, Folder 2)
      1923-1991
    - Nussbaum, Sidney Robert, 1946 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - O'Brien, Robert William, 1946 (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Ohlhorst, Roy Huga, 1946 (Box 11, Folder 5)
      1924-2004
    - Prier, James Eddy, 1946 (Box 11, Folder 6)
      1924-2012
    - Rubin, Gerard Jerry, 1946 (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - Ryan, William Gerard, 1946 (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - Salk, Herman Maurice, 1946 (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - Salk, Sylvia Burg, 1946 (Box 11, Folder 10)
      Twenty fifth woman graduate; contents incomplete
    - Sams, Jeanette, 1946 (Box 11, Folder 11)
      Twenty sixth woman graduate
    - Schenholm, Carl Lennart, 1946 (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - Schirmer, Robert George, 1946 (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - Steele, John Rae, 1946 (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - Tanneberger, Frank John, 1946 (Box 11, Folder 15)
    - Bailey, Jack William, 1947 (Box 11, Folder 16)
    - Benson, Jane Elizabeth Whallon, 1947 (Box 11, Folder 17)
      1926-2013
      Twenty seventh woman graduate
    - Benson, Kenneth Warner, 1947 (Box 11, Folder 18)
    - Bonelli, Benjamin Parish, 1947 (Box 11, Folder 19)
    - Campbell, Donn Brownell, 1947 (Box 11, Folder 20)
    - Carsley, Malcolm Bernard, 1947 (Box 11, Folder 21)
    - Cooper, Cecil Devour, Jr., 1947 (Box 11, Folder 22)
      1924-2003
    - Drazek, Francis Joseph, 1947 (Box 11, Folder 23)
      1925-2007
    - Feldman, Gilbert Jay, 1947 (Box 11, Folder 24)
    - Fish, Richard Alexander, 1947 (Box 11, Folder 25)
      1926-
    - Floyd, J. Mitchell, 1947 (Box 11, Folder 26)
      1920-1997
    - Geller, Estelle Hecht, 1947 (Box 11, Folder 27)
      1927-
      Twenty eighth woman graduate
    - Graves, John Henry, 1947 (Box 11, Folder 28)
    - Hallenbeck, Mary Catherine, 1947 (Box 11, Folder 29)
      Twenty ninth woman graduate
    - Kemen, Mathias John, Jr., 1947 (Box 11, Folder 30)
      1926-2009
    - Kendrick, John Wesley, 1947 (Box 11, Folder 31)
    - Leahy, John Robert, 1947 (Box 11, Folder 32)
      1916-2011
    - Mackey, Edwin Deforest, 1947 (Box 11, Folder 33)
    - Neserke, Edward Irvin, 1947 (Box 11, Folder 34)
      1922-1971
    - Newman, Ray Calvin, 1947 (Box 11, Folder 35)
      1924-2013
    - Ormsbee, Robert Wayne, 1947 (Box 11, Folder 36)
    - Phelps, John Lester, 1947 (Box 11, Folder 37)
    - Reighley, John Henry, Jr., 1947 (Box 11, Folder 38)
    - Rhode, Edward Albert, Jr., 1947 (Box 11, Folder 39)
    - Robinson, Elmer LeRoy, 1947 (Box 11, Folder 40)
    - Robinson, Ruth Elizabeth Jones, 1947 (Box 11, Folder 41)
      Thirtieth woman graduate
    - Roper, Calvin Barclay, 1947 (Box 11, Folder 42)
    - Rost, Robert Christopher, 1947 (Box 11, Folder 43)
      1924-2002
    - Rubin, Harry, 1947 (Box 11, Folder 44)
    - Safanie, Alvin Harold, 1947 (Box 11, Folder 45)